<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<language>
	<!-- Renegade Imperial Guard -->
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Corpses for the Corpse God"/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story0BeginningDescription" value="In your ten thousand years of war, you do not remember a worse sojourn in the Warp. Following Abaddon’s 13th Black Crusade in the days after the fall of Cadia, your cruiser jumped into the Warp—and became stuck there, like a wasp in amber.<br/><br/>Time became unreliable. Your crew and the ship itself became infested with the stuff of the Warp, possessed or mutated, until only a handful of your troops remained intact. When the cruiser finally burst from the warp above the Imperial world of Gladius Prime, it was a demonship and your surviving troops fled to the planet below.<br/><br/>After so many millennia though, you know that there is purpose to this. You have been tested and survived. You know that the Dark Gods had reason to send your warband to Gladius Prime and that you must discover it, or face their wrath."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story0Stage0Description" value="To a weaker eye, the planet would look devastated, with its imperial populace demoralised. To you, it looks ripe for corruption. You start immediately."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story0Stage1Description" value="Given your labours, a Chaos Spawn was hardly the blessing you’d hoped for. The writhing beast was once your Master of Executions. Now he—it—is chained in your compound, a twisted wreck that barely survives the mutations tearing it apart and reforming from moment to moment.<br/><br/>Your companion’s mind is gone. From its many mouths, however, he gibbers prophecy. “...the thousandth sword, the circuit completed, the gods in accord, infinity infested...” Your cultists interpret its words to warn of an Imperial attack—but, in its wake, revelation."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story0EndingDescription" value="The bound-daemonkin nailed to your throne howl to herald an arrival. Into your chamber strides the shifting Enioch, your Master of Possession. His familiars have been whispering since arriving on the planet and now talk of a great prospect for the planet, for any Lord with the power to take it. “Please the four Gods” hiss Enioch’s many voices. “And they will make this planet a fit home for a Daemon Prince.”<br/><br/>This planet is, in some sense you don’t bother to comprehend, alive. With the aid of Enioch and the guidance of the gods, you shall take it—and hopefully ascend to Daemonhood yourself."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story1" value="Chapter 2: The Rites of Tzeentch"/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story1BeginningDescription" value="There are no mirrors in your chambers. When the gods first blessed you with mutation, you shattered them all in your pride. But you have let the frames remain, to remind you of what you have become.<br/><br/>As you sit alone pondering Enioch’s untrustworthy words, the empty frames fill with a fleshy eye of Tzeentch, repeating endlessly, spilling trypophobic into the plasteel walls. Soon you are observed from every wall by the God’s blinking icon made flesh."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story1Stage0Description" value="You summon your aspirant Sorcerer. She performs rituals in front of the eyes, minor sacrifices, whispers secrets to them and listens as the eyelashes whisper together a language only she understands. She claims that the god demands tribute of you. That you must learn better to change."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story1Stage1Description" value="Your sorcerer returns, more twisted than before. She says that Fateweaver has spoken to her, oracular as ever. For now, she feels you are overstepping yourself—that you should honour Tzeentch with sacrifices, simple and complex. Overstepping yourself? How dare she! You narrow your eyes, knowing who that first sacrifice should be."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story1EndingDescription" value="You finger her eye sockets idly. The sorcerer served her purpose well, even if she was an unwilling sacrifice. You hope Tzeentch enjoys the savour of the soul of one of his own.<br/><br/>Her skull chatters to life in your gauntleted hand and whispers in the Changer’s voice. “Your defiance is… intriguing. This planet has a heart. We must change its beat for our own.” You smile as you crush the skull. This is a good start."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story2" value="Chapter 3: The Sacrament of Nurgle"/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story2BeginningDescription" value="The Master of Possession is announced at your chambers again. Enioch enters unhelmeted and even he seems momentarily set back by the eyes staring from the walls, the shattered skull in your hand. You relay Tzeentch’s message and he smiles, sly.<br/><br/>“Excellent. One god on side, my Lord, as far as the Changer can be trusted.” He peers closely at the blinking wall-eyes. “Our next prospect is more. Avuncular. And more obvious in his desires. All we need do is spread disease in his name, and we shall surely acquire his blessing.” An eye suddenly reveals inch-long teeth and snaps at him, before he crushes it with a fist."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story2Stage0Description" value="You dismiss him, commanding your cultists to perform the rituals of Nurgle. Soon, you hear the wails from the city-altars. Soon, flies begin landing on the eyes around you, laying eggs between frantically-fluttering lashes."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story2Stage1Description" value="The city heaves with tight-packed life, ideal for disease to spread—and your troops, already infected with Nurgle’s blight, stalk the streets like tallymen. Before nightfall, a pandemic rocks the city. Those who survive will always bear Nurgle’s blessings. As you lie, yourself feverish with a godsent malady, the fly-eaten eyes around you open like ragged mouths. A hundred throatless voices giggle a command. “Infect the swarm-god, spread disease even to the children of the Great Devourer, and receive my blessing”."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story2EndingDescription" value="You climb the corpses of the Tyranid megafauna. Such fools, the loyalists are, to fear these single-souled beasts. They die, they rot, like anything else. In the twitching heart of a flesh-building, you see the Mark of Nurgle. Bloated purple flies leave the ventricle walls and gather closely round you, a buzzing cloak. You know you have his blessing."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story3" value="Chapter 4: The Rituals of Khorne"/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story3BeginningDescription" value="Enioch stands in your chamber when you return, accompanied by a figure wreathed in technology. They’re inspecting the eye-wall, rotted and infected as it is. Before the new figure even turns, its mechatendrils and weapons are all aimed at you. A Warpsmith, then.<br/><br/>Enioch speaks “Two gods on side. The simplest challenge is next. All he wants is, well- You know.” He gestures at the wall, where the pustulent eyes are already bleeding. They start gushing. Flooding. Quickly the chamber is filling. The daemonkin at your throne panic as the blood rises. The blood is… green?"/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story3Stage0Description" value="The Warpsmith speaks. “Blood, #1F5429 not #67080B? Khorne 110010 fight. Orks! Located @ 52.941040, -1.174028.” Ork blood isn’t green, you know—you’ve killed enough—but you can see the reasoning. You order Enioch to start the rites of Khorne and the Warpsmith to prepare his machines for war."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story3Stage1Description" value="You have come to see what new horrors the Dark Mechanicum has created, ahead of the assault on the Orks. Instead, the Warpsmith seems intent on giving you a tour of his Infernal Fabricator. His flat machine tongue explanations of what should be unholy horrors frustrate and bore you. After he’s proudly presented the third identical soul-rending and daemon-entrapment station, you grab him by his fusion claws and crush him close.<br/><br/>“I don’t care.” You bellow. “Khorne doesn’t care. Nurgle doesn’t care. No-one cares. The greenskins must die! Build more daemon engines! Or-” He nods, implacable, and strides off on his mechatendrils.<br/><br/>Soon, you will have the forces to crush the Greenskins."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story3Stage2Description" value="The Warpsmith has worked hard, with help from the Master of Possession. With unholy ritual, infernal contracts and the lives of many slaves, he has produced serried ranks of half-daemon, half-machine monstrosities to crush the Greenskins into bloody paste for the Lord of Skulls’ pleasure. You order the assault."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story3EndingDescription" value="Your retinue stands on an escarpment, overlooking the Ork camp. The Daemon Engines are still happily stalking the few Greenskins who aren’t dead or disabled. Everywhere else is blood, pooling in the fighting pits and drops.<br/><br/>The Ork chief is still trying to crawl towards you, even with his limbs removed. They really are rather resilient. You sigh, reach down and hack his head off. It carries on trying to bite your ankles, until Enioch kicks it into the pool of blood. As the Ork head sinks, yelling incoherent threats, a daemonic mouth forms out of gore, swallows it and bellows “BLOOD FOR THE BLOOD GOD” before collapsing. Khorne, it appears, approves."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story4" value="Chapter 5: The Liturgy of Slaanesh"/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story4BeginningDescription" value="Do you fear walking back into your chambers? Perhaps the gods are playing with you, not choosing you for ascension? No, you are a Chaos Lord, and you have no choice but to go on—to step backwards, is to demand spawnhood like the Master of Executions. That said, Enioch accompanies you in.<br/><br/>You step in the room. The hall is long and quiet. The eyes are quivering but shut. The floor is clear of blood and pus. Even your horrid daemonkin seem intact, purring. It all is *too* calm.<br/><br/>Then you see why. A daemon sits on your throne. Your heart catches. Beauty personified. Alabaster skin, iridescent chitin, eyes faceted like jewels. You struggle for control at its scent, lick dry lips at the erotic curve of its impossible claws. As you struggle with yourself, the walleyes peel open and distorted tongues, limbs and organs emerge, straining for your touch."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story4Stage0Description" value="“Little lord. You want Slaanesh’s blessing, little Lord?” purrs the Enrapturess, “Come, your task is simple. Teach the machines. Teach them to suffer and to love.” Enioch groans in ecstasy and you turn to silence him with a growl. When you turn back, the room is empty once more. You slump on your skull-encrusted throne and order the rites of Slaanesh to begin."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story4Stage1Description" value="Outside your denuded chamber, the city groans in a midnight ecstasy. The Lord of Excess, She Who Thirsts owns it tonight. Every form of depravity, every torture, every transgression happens in the city streets. Your dreams are troubled, delightful. In the morning, you find a gift at your door. And the Warpsmith waiting, untouched by the lust and horror, with coordinates of a Necron tomb."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story4EndingDescription" value="You’re not sure whether you taught the Necrons to love—but you certainly taught them suffering. Trapping their soulless bodies from escape, experimenting with tortures and horrors, watching the Warpsmith cutting their fleshmetal open to hyperstimulate their pleasure centres… before this day you wouldn’t have said you could make a Necron suffer like this, couldn’t drive a Necron mad with lust.<br/><br/>You feel a heavy crustacean-like claw rest on your shoulder and a rush of lust. And a sultry voice whispers into your ear, “congratulations, little Lord.”"/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story5" value="Chapter 6: A True Daemon World"/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story5BeginningDescription" value="The preparations are made. The gods have all signalled your favour (and not just on the walls of your chamber.) Now comes your moment.<br/><br/>You invoke the favour of each god in turn—Khorne, Tzeentch, Nurgle, Slaanesh. Across the surface of the planet, a great sigil of Chaos is drawn by their unholy power, encompassing the infinity circuit at the planet’s core."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story5Stage0Description" value="The final stage is to pour the spirit of a true Daemon into the machinery. Enioch’s wheedling and the Gods’ blessings have secured you the service of an ancient Daemon Prince. He is the centre of the star—the focus, upon which the Warpsmith and Master of Possession will work. Unwilling, but compelled by the gods, he aids you."/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story5Stage1Description" value="Now the ritual begins in earnest. The Master of Possession and Warpsmith know what to do. The Warpsmith’s arcane machinery attunes itself to the planet’s pylons and circuits, whilst Enioch orders cultists to each point of the star. Through blood and brute worship, you will complete the ritual and infest the Old One’s ancient defenses.<br/><br/>Finally, the fools of the Imperium awake to your presence. But are they too late?"/>
	<entry name="ChaosGuard/Story5EndingDescription" value="Everything happens at once. Enioch’s wry face collapses into dust even as he invokes the gods. The warp swallows the Daemon Prince, purple flames immolate the praying cultists, and the Warpsmith is pulled into his arcane machinery, gibbering 1s and 0s. Only you survive, becalmed in the storm.<br/><br/>Failure—and eternal torment—is a moment away.<br/><br/>But, after ten thousand years of striving and horror, you feel the gods’ touch upon you. Dark wings sprout from your back, your limbs grow monstrous. You are a newborn Daemon Prince of Chaos Undivided, howling your birth to a dying world.<br/><br/>Your freedom lasts but a second. The ritual drags you into the planet’s core, consuming the ancient spirits hiding there. You are the planet now, a true daemon world. Your unholy presence pulls it and its billion surviving souls into the Warp. There, you will torment them eternally."/>

<!-- Renegade Imperial Guard -->
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story0" value="Chapter 1: Corpses for the Corpse God"/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story0BeginningDescription" value="In your ten thousand years of war, you do not remember a worse sojourn in the Warp. Following Abaddon’s 13th Black Crusade in the days after the fall of Cadia, your cruiser jumped into the Warp—and became stuck there, like a wasp in amber.<br/><br/>Time became unreliable. Your crew and the ship itself became infested with the stuff of the Warp, possessed or mutated, until only a handful of your troops remained intact. When the cruiser finally burst from the warp above the Imperial world of Gladius Prime, it was a demonship and your surviving troops fled to the planet below.<br/><br/>After so many millennia though, you know that there is purpose to this. You have been tested and survived. You know that the Dark Gods had reason to send your warband to Gladius Prime and that you must discover it, or face their wrath."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story0Stage0Description" value="To a weaker eye, the planet would look devastated, with its imperial populace demoralised. To you, it looks ripe for corruption. You start immediately."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story0Stage1Description" value="Given your labours, a Chaos Spawn was hardly the blessing you’d hoped for. The writhing beast was once your Master of Executions. Now he—it—is chained in your compound, a twisted wreck that barely survives the mutations tearing it apart and reforming from moment to moment.<br/><br/>Your companion’s mind is gone. From its many mouths, however, he gibbers prophecy. “...the thousandth sword, the circuit completed, the gods in accord, infinity infested...” Your cultists interpret its words to warn of an Imperial attack—but, in its wake, revelation."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story0EndingDescription" value="The bound-daemonkin nailed to your throne howl to herald an arrival. Into your chamber strides the shifting Enioch, your Master of Possession. His familiars have been whispering since arriving on the planet and now talk of a great prospect for the planet, for any Lord with the power to take it. “Please the four Gods” hiss Enioch’s many voices. “And they will make this planet a fit home for a Daemon Prince.”<br/><br/>This planet is, in some sense you don’t bother to comprehend, alive. With the aid of Enioch and the guidance of the gods, you shall take it—and hopefully ascend to Daemonhood yourself."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story1" value="Chapter 2: The Rites of Tzeentch"/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story1BeginningDescription" value="There are no mirrors in your chambers. When the gods first blessed you with mutation, you shattered them all in your pride. But you have let the frames remain, to remind you of what you have become.<br/><br/>As you sit alone pondering Enioch’s untrustworthy words, the empty frames fill with a fleshy eye of Tzeentch, repeating endlessly, spilling trypophobic into the plasteel walls. Soon you are observed from every wall by the God’s blinking icon made flesh."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story1Stage0Description" value="You summon your aspirant Sorcerer. She performs rituals in front of the eyes, minor sacrifices, whispers secrets to them and listens as the eyelashes whisper together a language only she understands. She claims that the god demands tribute of you. That you must learn better to change."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story1Stage1Description" value="Your sorcerer returns, more twisted than before. She says that Fateweaver has spoken to her, oracular as ever. For now, she feels you are overstepping yourself—that you should honour Tzeentch with sacrifices, simple and complex. Overstepping yourself? How dare she! You narrow your eyes, knowing who that first sacrifice should be."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story1EndingDescription" value="You finger her eye sockets idly. The sorcerer served her purpose well, even if she was an unwilling sacrifice. You hope Tzeentch enjoys the savour of the soul of one of his own.<br/><br/>Her skull chatters to life in your gauntleted hand and whispers in the Changer’s voice. “Your defiance is… intriguing. This planet has a heart. We must change its beat for our own.” You smile as you crush the skull. This is a good start."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story2" value="Chapter 3: The Sacrament of Nurgle"/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story2BeginningDescription" value="The Master of Possession is announced at your chambers again. Enioch enters unhelmeted and even he seems momentarily set back by the eyes staring from the walls, the shattered skull in your hand. You relay Tzeentch’s message and he smiles, sly.<br/><br/>“Excellent. One god on side, my Lord, as far as the Changer can be trusted.” He peers closely at the blinking wall-eyes. “Our next prospect is more. Avuncular. And more obvious in his desires. All we need do is spread disease in his name, and we shall surely acquire his blessing.” An eye suddenly reveals inch-long teeth and snaps at him, before he crushes it with a fist."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story2Stage0Description" value="You dismiss him, commanding your cultists to perform the rituals of Nurgle. Soon, you hear the wails from the city-altars. Soon, flies begin landing on the eyes around you, laying eggs between frantically-fluttering lashes."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story2Stage1Description" value="The city heaves with tight-packed life, ideal for disease to spread—and your troops, already infected with Nurgle’s blight, stalk the streets like tallymen. Before nightfall, a pandemic rocks the city. Those who survive will always bear Nurgle’s blessings. As you lie, yourself feverish with a godsent malady, the fly-eaten eyes around you open like ragged mouths. A hundred throatless voices giggle a command. “Infect the swarm-god, spread disease even to the children of the Great Devourer, and receive my blessing”."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story2EndingDescription" value="You climb the corpses of the Tyranid megafauna. Such fools, the loyalists are, to fear these single-souled beasts. They die, they rot, like anything else. In the twitching heart of a flesh-building, you see the Mark of Nurgle. Bloated purple flies leave the ventricle walls and gather closely round you, a buzzing cloak. You know you have his blessing."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story3" value="Chapter 4: The Rituals of Khorne"/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story3BeginningDescription" value="Enioch stands in your chamber when you return, accompanied by a figure wreathed in technology. They’re inspecting the eye-wall, rotted and infected as it is. Before the new figure even turns, its mechatendrils and weapons are all aimed at you. A Warpsmith, then.<br/><br/>Enioch speaks “Two gods on side. The simplest challenge is next. All he wants is, well- You know.” He gestures at the wall, where the pustulent eyes are already bleeding. They start gushing. Flooding. Quickly the chamber is filling. The daemonkin at your throne panic as the blood rises. The blood is… green?"/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story3Stage0Description" value="The Warpsmith speaks. “Blood, #1F5429 not #67080B? Khorne 110010 fight. Orks! Located @ 52.941040, -1.174028.” Ork blood isn’t green, you know—you’ve killed enough—but you can see the reasoning. You order Enioch to start the rites of Khorne and the Warpsmith to prepare his machines for war."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story3Stage1Description" value="You have come to see what new horrors the Dark Mechanicum has created, ahead of the assault on the Orks. Instead, the Warpsmith seems intent on giving you a tour of his Infernal Fabricator. His flat machine tongue explanations of what should be unholy horrors frustrate and bore you. After he’s proudly presented the third identical soul-rending and daemon-entrapment station, you grab him by his fusion claws and crush him close.<br/><br/>“I don’t care.” You bellow. “Khorne doesn’t care. Nurgle doesn’t care. No-one cares. The greenskins must die! Build more daemon engines! Or-” He nods, implacable, and strides off on his mechatendrils.<br/><br/>Soon, you will have the forces to crush the Greenskins."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story3Stage2Description" value="The Warpsmith has worked hard, with help from the Master of Possession. With unholy ritual, infernal contracts and the lives of many slaves, he has produced serried ranks of half-daemon, half-machine monstrosities to crush the Greenskins into bloody paste for the Lord of Skulls’ pleasure. You order the assault."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story3EndingDescription" value="Your retinue stands on an escarpment, overlooking the Ork camp. The Daemon Engines are still happily stalking the few Greenskins who aren’t dead or disabled. Everywhere else is blood, pooling in the fighting pits and drops.<br/><br/>The Ork chief is still trying to crawl towards you, even with his limbs removed. They really are rather resilient. You sigh, reach down and hack his head off. It carries on trying to bite your ankles, until Enioch kicks it into the pool of blood. As the Ork head sinks, yelling incoherent threats, a daemonic mouth forms out of gore, swallows it and bellows “BLOOD FOR THE BLOOD GOD” before collapsing. Khorne, it appears, approves."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story4" value="Chapter 5: The Liturgy of Slaanesh"/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story4BeginningDescription" value="Do you fear walking back into your chambers? Perhaps the gods are playing with you, not choosing you for ascension? No, you are a Chaos Lord, and you have no choice but to go on—to step backwards, is to demand spawnhood like the Master of Executions. That said, Enioch accompanies you in.<br/><br/>You step in the room. The hall is long and quiet. The eyes are quivering but shut. The floor is clear of blood and pus. Even your horrid daemonkin seem intact, purring. It all is *too* calm.<br/><br/>Then you see why. A daemon sits on your throne. Your heart catches. Beauty personified. Alabaster skin, iridescent chitin, eyes faceted like jewels. You struggle for control at its scent, lick dry lips at the erotic curve of its impossible claws. As you struggle with yourself, the walleyes peel open and distorted tongues, limbs and organs emerge, straining for your touch."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story4Stage0Description" value="“Little lord. You want Slaanesh’s blessing, little Lord?” purrs the Enrapturess, “Come, your task is simple. Teach the machines. Teach them to suffer and to love.” Enioch groans in ecstasy and you turn to silence him with a growl. When you turn back, the room is empty once more. You slump on your skull-encrusted throne and order the rites of Slaanesh to begin."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story4Stage1Description" value="Outside your denuded chamber, the city groans in a midnight ecstasy. The Lord of Excess, She Who Thirsts owns it tonight. Every form of depravity, every torture, every transgression happens in the city streets. Your dreams are troubled, delightful. In the morning, you find a gift at your door. And the Warpsmith waiting, untouched by the lust and horror, with coordinates of a Necron tomb."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story4EndingDescription" value="You’re not sure whether you taught the Necrons to love—but you certainly taught them suffering. Trapping their soulless bodies from escape, experimenting with tortures and horrors, watching the Warpsmith cutting their fleshmetal open to hyperstimulate their pleasure centres… before this day you wouldn’t have said you could make a Necron suffer like this, couldn’t drive a Necron mad with lust.<br/><br/>You feel a heavy crustacean-like claw rest on your shoulder and a rush of lust. And a sultry voice whispers into your ear, “congratulations, little Lord.”"/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story5" value="Chapter 6: A True Daemon World"/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story5BeginningDescription" value="The preparations are made. The gods have all signalled your favour (and not just on the walls of your chamber.) Now comes your moment.<br/><br/>You invoke the favour of each god in turn—Khorne, Tzeentch, Nurgle, Slaanesh. Across the surface of the planet, a great sigil of Chaos is drawn by their unholy power, encompassing the infinity circuit at the planet’s core."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story5Stage0Description" value="The final stage is to pour the spirit of a true Daemon into the machinery. Enioch’s wheedling and the Gods’ blessings have secured you the service of an ancient Daemon Prince. He is the centre of the star—the focus, upon which the Warpsmith and Master of Possession will work. Unwilling, but compelled by the gods, he aids you."/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story5Stage1Description" value="Now the ritual begins in earnest. The Master of Possession and Warpsmith know what to do. The Warpsmith’s arcane machinery attunes itself to the planet’s pylons and circuits, whilst Enioch orders cultists to each point of the star. Through blood and brute worship, you will complete the ritual and infest the Old One’s ancient defenses.<br/><br/>Finally, the fools of the Imperium awake to your presence. But are they too late?"/>
	<entry name="traitorguard/Story5EndingDescription" value="Everything happens at once. Enioch’s wry face collapses into dust even as he invokes the gods. The warp swallows the Daemon Prince, purple flames immolate the praying cultists, and the Warpsmith is pulled into his arcane machinery, gibbering 1s and 0s. Only you survive, becalmed in the storm.<br/><br/>Failure—and eternal torment—is a moment away.<br/><br/>But, after ten thousand years of striving and horror, you feel the gods’ touch upon you. Dark wings sprout from your back, your limbs grow monstrous. You are a newborn Daemon Prince of Chaos Undivided, howling your birth to a dying world.<br/><br/>Your freedom lasts but a second. The ritual drags you into the planet’s core, consuming the ancient spirits hiding there. You are the planet now, a true daemon world. Your unholy presence pulls it and its billion surviving souls into the Warp. There, you will torment them eternally."/>


</language>
