<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<language>
	<entry name="AstraMilitarum/SabreGunPlatformCommonFlavor" value="Its heavy armour plates provide ample cover, while its gyroscopic platform allows for rapid target acquistion when assaulted on multiple fronts. However, the platform cannot be moved without being completely disassambled. When preparing for the enemy, this is inconvenient but managable. When a retreat is called during battle, however, the crew knows they'll either have to scuttle the weapons or fight to the bitter end. Dying with honour requires no explanation; cowardly allowing Imperial equipment to be captured leaves room for none."/>

	<entry name="AstraMilitarum/SabreGunPlatform" value="Sabre Gun Platform (<string name='Weapons/SabreTwinLinkedHeavyStubber'/>)"/>
	<entry name="AstraMilitarum/SabreGunPlatformDescription" value="Immobile, manned anti-air weapons emplacement. Performance improves as more crew operates it."/>
	<entry name="AstraMilitarum/SabreGunPlatformFlavor" value="Guardsmen fear the skies. Enemies on the ground, horrifying as they are, can be shot and stabbed. Enemies in the air are much more difficult to fight back against, and without support from the Navis Imperialis, airborne foes have near-free reign to bombard helpless Guardsmen. When defending strategic points, the Astra Militarum has been known to construct Sabre Gun Platforms for added firepower. They can be equipped with a variety of typical Imperial armaments, but most-beloved are the quad-mounted Heavy Stubbers. Sheer volume of fire creates a wall of bullets for enemy aircraft to crash into. <string name='Units/AstraMilitarum/SabreGunPlatformCommonFlavor'/>"/>
	<entry name="AstraMilitarum/SabreGunPlatformLascannon" value="Sabre Gun Platform (<string name='Weapons/SabreTwinLinkedLascannon'/>)"/>
	<entry name="AstraMilitarum/SabreGunPlatformLascannonDescription" value="Immobile, manned anti-armour weapons emplacement. Performance improves as more crew operates it."/>
	<entry name="AstraMilitarum/SabreGunPlatformLascannonFlavor" value="The Infantry of the Astra Militarum are no strangers to holding ground. Trenches are dug, sandbags are filled, and barbed wire is strung about the perimeter. Defences funnel the enemy into kill-zones, where fields of overlapping fire can easily cut down infantry. However, armour can ram a hole in these lines, allowing hordes to pour through. Heavy Weapons Teams can fire from multiple angles, but a properly placed fixed turret can be even more devastating. <string name='Units/AstraMilitarum/SabreGunPlatformCommonFlavor'/>"/>
</language>
